Welcome to Adventure!
Start the game with start.py


This is a game based off the first real program I ever created back when I was like 10.
That game was a choose your own adventure game titled Adventure.py.
The file is included, mostly unedited(black reformatted it to fit pep8 but otherwise unedited.)
It unfortunately doesnt work(I'm not sure how it ever did) so dont try to run it.


Sadly I was unable to come up with some useful tests because the program is literally just displaying 
prewritten dialogue to the output when you click a button.


Lots of modules. I realised the importance of modules while working on this.


Also I have fallen in love with black. VS code allows you to edit the way it works so I can make
it automatically format to my style of coding. Doesnt remove trailing whitespace though ):


Please play the game before looking into the code because it spoils where all the deaths are.


Also sorry the choices never make it past level 4, I ran out of time to code in more story.


I will add a diagram showing the entire story and add some more story to the game on friday.